It's all over.
I will protect you.
Wait for me.
Officer Zhuang.
I plead guilty.
I killed Mu Weijie.
Is this world
always black and white?
Is a murderer always a bad person?
Is a victim always a good person?
You have no idea
how much damage Mu Weijie
has done to me.
Do you know
what chastity and self-esteem mean to a girl?
How precious it is?
Mu Weijie took nude photos of me.
Faced with his threats
and my mother's expectations,
I had no choice but to submit to him.
But I didn't expect
that it would only make him worse
and lead to a darker tomorrow.
Mu Weijie, what are you doing?
Mu Weijie!
Let me go!
He is an absolute monster.
Not only did he satisfy his own lust,
he also found thugs to humiliate me
to stimulate his creative inspiration.
Behave.
Just like that,
I became the Danaë in Mu Weijie's paintings.
During those days,
I lived in a daze,
like a walking corpse.
I hated myself for being like that,
and I also hated the Danaë in the painting.
I wanted
to get rid of this demon with my own hands.
When he died,
I was actually very happy.
Because I was finally free.
I plead guilty.
Please don't take her away.
Wait a minute.
Officer Zhuang.
I need a favor from you.
You must tell everyone the truth about this
and make it public.
I'm not afraid.
We are the victims.
If we don't speak up,
thousands of monsters like Mu Weijie
will get away with it.
We won't be able to bear it.
You must get justice for Rongrong
and clear her name.
I promise you.
Based on what you went through,
we have filed a public prosecution against Mu Weijie.
After receiving the compensation,
your mother will also be well taken care of.
So you don't need to worry too much.
Oh, right.
As for the three men who assaulted you,
we have already detained them.
What about Rongrong?
Is she okay?
She's doing well.
She has gone home to recuperate.
Thank you, Officer Zhuang.
There's one more question I want to ask you.
How did you come up with
such a method to kill someone?
What makes you think I couldn't come up with it?
With your life experience
and at your age,
you wouldn't have thought of it.
Tell me,
who helped you behind the scenes?
Actually, I don't know who he is either.
He contacted me first.
As if telling a story,
he told me the killing method
and crime details.
Very carefully.
His profile picture
is a lighthouse.
The accident was the lighthouse's design.
You handled this case beautifully.
The Bureau is very satisfied with the efficiency
of your accident investigation team.
Keep up the good work.
What's wrong?
You guys are usually fooling around.
You cracked the case today.
Why the long faces?
I just can't figure it out.
Someone like Mu Weijie is rich
and has both fame and fortune.
How could he do such a heartless thing?
I really can't imagine.
If I were one of those girls,
would I still have the courage to live on?
I'm sorry.
Whenever I think about these things,
I just can't be happy.
We are police officers.
What you just mentioned,
we've seen a lot over the years.
For the horrible things they've suffered,
someone has to be held accountable.
You have already done very well.
Don't be so down.
Tell me, in this world,
how many people are out there suffering?
Why is it
that they choose to use their own methods
and refuse to trust us?
In this case,
what each girl goes through
is a lifelong game of Russian roulette.
They obviously did nothing wrong,
yet they are threatened and persecuted.
Suffering humiliation,
they dared not speak up.
They started to doubt life,
believing they were just unlucky
to be chosen by the devil.
Until they saw each other,
they finally understood
that in the roulette of fate,
no one is lucky.
Perhaps,
every girl knew what Xu Qiaoyue was going to do.
But they were still willing to hold up an umbrella for Xu Qiaoyue
to shield her from the storm.
The accident was Lighthouse's design.
There's no time. They found me.
I can't leave.
Which will come first, tomorrow or an accident?
Anyway,
celebrating the official establishment of our Accident Investigation Team
is the most important thing.
Let's welcome Mr. Cheng Mo.
Welcome.
Welcome, Mr. Cheng.
Cheers.
Welcome.
Welcome, Mr. Cheng.
Come on, say a few words to everyone.
Thank you.
That's it?
That's it.
Good.
Well said, Mr. Cheng.
Well said.
After welcoming Mr. Cheng,
let me propose a toast.
This second toast
is to celebrate the Mu Weijie case
being successfully closed.
Although the process was bumpy,
the truth finally came out, right?
In all my years as a police officer,
this is the most beautifully handled case.
Cheers.
Wait.
I also want to say something.
Go ahead.
Here's the thing.
Cheng Mo was amazing this time.
Especially your
deduction of combining five pills into one.
It was a stroke of genius.
But,
Captain,
I actually thought of the same thing as Cheng Mo long ago.
What are you doing?
Come on,
you always talk the most.
In this case,
you are a great hero.
So,
no matter what,
you still need to say a few more words to us.
How can just a 'thank you' be enough?
No way.
Say something.
Share with us.
Actually,
I'm very happy to meet everyone.
Knowing you all
is our destiny.
Of course,
establishing the Accident Investigation Team
for us,
is a mission.
So,
we must uphold justice
and punish the evil.
Let the truth come out in every case,
bring justice to every case,
and to the families and victims.
A fair chance,
with no regrets.
Okay.